[MUSIC]
[背景音乐] 翻译: RyukaSuu |审阅: 19waa Coursera Global Translator Community
In the regression model, we talked about predicting house prices and
在回归模型中
fitting a regression model for that and
我们讨论了通过拟合一个回归模型来预测房价
we measured the error in terms of sum-squared errors.
我们也用 误差平方和 来测量（模型）误差
Here in classification, our errors are a little different because we
这里 在分类问题中 我们的误差有所不同
are talking about what inputs we get correct and which inputs we get wrong.
因为我们在讨论对哪些输入我们（预测）对了 哪些错了
So let's talk a little bit about measuring error in classification.
所以我们先来谈谈分类问题的误差测量
So when I learn a classifier, I'm given a set of input data.
当我学习一个 分类器 的时候  我有一组输入数据
So these are sentences that have been marked to say positive or negative
这些数据是一些句子 被标注了是正面或是负面情绪
sentiment, and as in regression, we split it into a training set and a test set.
就像在回归模型里一样 我们把数据分成训练集和测试集
I feed the training set to the classifier I'm trying to learn and
我用训练集去训练我要学习的分类器
that algorithm is actually going to learn the weights for words.
那个（学习）算法会学习每个字的权重
So for example it's going to learn that good has a weight 1.0.
举例来说 它会习得 “good" ("好")这个词权重为1.0
Awesome, 1.7.
"awesome"(”棒") 这个词的权重是 1.7
Bad, -1.0.
"bad" ("坏") 的权重为 -1.0
And awful, -3.3.
"awful" ("糟") 的权重是 -3.3
And then, these weights are going to be used to score every element in
接下来 这些权重会被用来给测试集里面的句子打分
the test set and evaluate how good we're doing in terms of classification.
测试集用来评估我们的分类效果如何
So lets talk about what that evaluation looks like.
所以我们来谈谈 评估 是怎么做的
Let's discuss how we measure error, in fact,
先看看当我们做分类的时候
classification error, when we're doing this classification.
我们怎么测量分类误差
So we're getting a set of test examples of the form,
我们的测试集类似这样的形式: 寿司真不错
sushi was great, is a positive sentence, and we're trying to figure out how many
这是一个正面情绪的句子 我们要弄清楚
of these test sentences we get correct and how many do we get make mistakes on.
测试集里的句子我们正确分类了多少 错误有多少
So what we are going to do is take the sentence sushi is great and
所以我们要做的是 把"寿司真不错" 这个句子
feed it through the classifier, through the learned classifier.
交给分类器 那个学习过的分类器
But we don't want the learned classifier to actually see the true label.
但我们不会把真标签 ("正面情绪") 提供给这个分类器
We're gonna see if it gets the true label right.
我们要看看这个分类器是否正确分类
So we're gonna hide that true label.
所以我们把真标签藏起来
So the sentence gets fed to the learned classifier while the true label is hidden.
所以分类器所得到句子的真标签是隐藏的
And now given the sentence, we're gonna predict y hat as being positive.
对这个句子 我们预测分类结果y帽是正面情绪
So we leave this as a positive sentence and so, we've made a correct prediction.
我们相信这个句子情绪为正面 因此我们的预测是正确的
So the number of correct sentences goes up by one.
所以 正确分类的个数 加一
Now let's take another sentence, another test example.
我们再来看看另一个句子 另一个测试例子
So let's say you say the food was okay as a negative sentence.
比如说 食物还行吧 是一个负面情绪的句子
So that's a bit of a ambiguous sentence but
这句子情绪有点模糊
it's been labeled as negative in the training set.
但在训练集里面 它的真标签 是负面
So now I feed the sentence to the classifier, I hide the label.
我把这句子输入给分类器  它的真标签是隐藏的
And let's see what the classifier does.
让我们看看分类器的结果是什么
In this case, cuz the food was okay can be revealed as positive,
在这个例子里 因为 "食物还行" 也可以被认为是正面的
maybe it makes a prediction that this is positive sentence I made a mistake,
因此有可能分类器认为它是正面情绪 这时它就犯了一个错误
cuz the true label is negative.
因为真标签是 负面
So say hey, mistake was made.
所以出现了错误
We now have one more mistake.
分类错误数加一
So we have one correct classification and one mistake.
所以我们现在有一个正确分类和一个错误分类
Now, we do this for every sentence in the corpus.
我们把测试集里每个句子都这么来一遍
There are two common measures of quality in classification.
有两种常见的测量分类效果的方法
So for example, one of them is the notion of error.
其中一个是 误差率
So error measures, the fraction of the test examples that we make mistakes on.
误差率测量的是我们分类错了的句子比例
So what we just do is say, out of all of the sentences that are classified,
也就是 在所有被分类的句子里
how many mistakes there are made, so number of mistakes, and
我们犯了多少错误
I divide that by the total number of test sentences.
用分类错误数 除以 总句子数
So for example if there were 100 test sentences and
举例来说 假如我们有100个句子
I made ten mistakes then our error would be 0.1 or 10%.
我们分类错了10个 那么误差率就是 0.1 或说10%
Now the best possible error that I can make is zero basically,
可以看出误差率最低为0
I make no mistakes.
就是说我一个错误都没犯的情况
Now, it's common to instead of talk about error,
另一个常见测量分类效果的方法
to also talk about accuracy of your classifier.
是 分类器的正确率
So accuracy is exactly opposite of that.
正确率正好是误差率的反面
So, in accuracy, instead of measuring the number of errors,
和测量我们分类错了多少句子相反
we measure the number of correct classifications.
它表示的是 我们测量正确的分类数目
So the ratio here is number
所以正确率 就是
of correct divided by total
分类正确的句子数
number of sentences.
除以 总句子数
And unlike error where the best possible value is zero, in terms of accuracy,
如果说最好的错误率为0
the best possible value is 1, I've got all the sentences right.
那么最好的正确率就是1 就是我们所有句子都分类正确了
And in fact there's a really natural relationship between the two.
实际上这两者之间有本质的关系
We know that error = 1-
误差率 = 1-正确率
[MUSIC]
[背景音乐] 翻译: RyukaSuu |审阅: 19waa Coursera Global Translator Community